Register of the Russia. Posol'stvo (U.S.) Records, 1897-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- Military Agent Office File, 1915-1921.
  - General (Box 236)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - 1913-1920 (Folder 9)
        - 1914-1915 (Box 237, Folder 1-2)
          Available on microfilm reels 289 and 290
        - 1917
          - August-November (Folder 3)
            Available on microfilm reel 290
          - November-December (Folder 4)
        - 1918 (Folder 5)
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 6)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 7-8)
        - 1920 (Folder 9)
          Available on microfilm reel 291
        - 1920-1921 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Register (Folder 2)
      - Telegrams
        - General
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 3)
          - 1915
            - January-April (Folder 4)
            - March-May (Folder 5)
              Available on microfilm reel 292
            - May-July (Folder 6)
        - Incoming
          - 1915
            - July (Folder 7)
            - July-August (Box 239, Folder 1)
            - August (Folder 2)
            - August-September (Folder 3)
              Available on microfilm reel 293
            - September (Folder 4-5)
            - September-October (Folder 6)
          - 1915-1916 (Folder 7)
          - 1919 (Folder 8)
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 9)
        - Outgoing (Box 240)
          - 1915
            - July-August (Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 294
            - July-October (Folder 2)
          - 1915-1916 (Folder 3)
          - 1919-1921 (Folder 4)
    - Financial record
      - General
        - 1917-1918 (Folder 5)
        - 1919-1921 (Folder 6)
      - Bank statement (Folder 7)
      - Cash books (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 295
      - Creditor's book (Folder 9)
    - Memoranda--see Orders and memoranda (Box 241)
    - Orders and memoranda (Folder 1)
    - Register of files
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Division of Supplies--see Russian Supply Committee and Division of Supplies
      - Russian Supply Committee (Folder 3)
      - Russian Supply Committee and Division of Supplies (Folder 4)
    - Reports--see Correspondence
  - Aero Club of America (Folder 5)
  - Akintievskii, G., Lieutenant-General
    - General (Folder 6)
    - "National Army and the Czechoslovaks, Summer, 1918." Typewritten copies (in English and Russian) (Folder 7)
  - American Central Committee for Russian Relief (Folder 8)
  - Bosporus. Maps (Folder 9)
  - Censorship--see Russian Red Cross/Censorship
  - Colby, Bainbridge--see Poland -- war with Russia/Note of August 1920
  - Communication with Russia
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Ciphers (Folder 11)
  - Composition and structure
    - 1916-1917 (Folder 12)
    - 1917-1921 (Folder 13)
      Available on microfilm reel 296
  - European War, 1914-1918
    - General (Folder 14)
      - 1914-1915 (Folder 15)
      - 1915
      - 1916 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - 1916-1917 (Folder 2)
      - 1916-1918 (Folder 3)
    - Russia
      - Contribution to Allies' victory. Clippings, correspondence, printed matter, reports
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 4)
        - 1919-1921 (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 297
      - Foreign military supplies
        - General (Folder 6-7)
        - Allied Machinery Company of America (Folder 8)
        - Canadian Car and Foundry Company
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 9)
          - 1915 (Folder 10)
        - Commercial products (Box 243)
          - General
            - 1914-1915 (Folder 1-2)
            - 1915
              - May-October (Folder 3)
                Available on microfilm reel 298
              - August (Folder 4)
          - Brass sheets (Folder 5)
          - Cartridges--see guns and cartridges
          - Cloth (Folder 6)
          - Explosives (Folder 7-9)
          - Guns and cartridges (Folder 10)
          - Horseshoes (Box 244, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 299
          - Rifles (Folder 2)
          - Trucks (Folder 3)
        - Russian Government Committee, London (Folder 4)
        - Special Commission on State Defense, Petrograd (Folder 5)
      - United States, Reservists and would-be mercenaries in the (Folder 6)
      - War Ministry, Petrograd
        - Orders
          - 1914 (Folder 7)
          - 1914-1915 (Folder 8)
          - 1915
            - February-March (Folder 9)
            - April-May (Folder 10)
              Available on microfilm reel 300
          - 1916-1917 (Folder 11)
        - War news (Box 245)
          - 1914
            - November (Folder 1)
            - December (Folder 2)
          - 1915
            - January (Folder 3)
            - February (Folder 4)
            - March (Folder 5)
            - April (Folder 6)
            - May (Folder 7)
              Available on microfilm reel 301
            - June (Box 246, Folder 1)
            - July (Folder 2)
            - August (Folder 3)
            - September (Folder 4)
            - October (Folder 5)
              Available on microfilm reel 302
            - November (Folder 6)
            - December (Folder 7)
          - 1916 (Box 247)
            - January (Folder 1)
            - February (Folder 2)
            - March (Folder 3)
            - April (Folder 4)
            - May (Folder 5)
              Available on microfilm reel 303
            - June (Folder 6)
            - July (Folder 7)
            - August (Box 248, Folder 1)
            - September-October (Folder 2)
            - November (Folder 3)
            - December (Folder 4)
              Available on microfilm reel 304
          - 1917
            - January (Folder 5)
            - February (Box 249, Folder 1)
            - March (Folder 2)
            - April (Folder 3)
            - May-June (Folder 4)
            - July (Folder 5)
              Available on microfilm reel 305
            - August (Folder 6)
            - September (Box 250, Folder 1)
            - October
              - 1-13 (Folder 2)
              - 20-31 (Folder 3)
            - November (Folder 4)
  - Lebedev, Vladimir--see Akintievskii, G., Lieutenant-Colonel/ General
  - Mexican armed forces--see United States/Armed forces/ General/Reports/General
  - Odinstov, Colonel, ed., Voorushennye sily Severo- Amerikanskikh Soedinenykh Shtatov i drugikh gosudarstv Ameriki. St. Petersburg, 1910 (Folder 5)
  - Office supply (Folder 6)
  - Poland -- war with Russia. (see also Russian intelligence service/World politics)
    - Clippings, 1920
      - February-August (Folder 7)
      - March-May (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 306
      - May-June (Folder 9)
    - Notes of August 1920 by Bainbridge Colby (Folder 10)
  - Russia
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Counterrevolutionary movements (Box 251)
      - General. (see also Military Agent Office File/ Russia intelligence service/World politics)
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 1)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 2-3)
          Available on microfilm reels 306 and 307
        - 1920-1921 (Folder 4)
          Available on microfilm reel 307
      - Administration of the Commander-in-Chief's Chief Representative of the Russian Army to the Government of French Republic. Military and political reports, Paris Republic. Military and political reports
        - 1919
          - August-October (Folder 5)
          - October-November (Folder 6)
          - November-December (Box 252, Folder 1)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 2-3)
          Available on microfilm reel 308
        - 1920
          - March-May (Folder 4)
          - May-August (Folder 5)
          - September-October (Folder 6)
          - November (Folder 7)
      - Czechoslovaks--see Military Agent Office File/ Akintievskii, G., Lieutenant-Colonel, "National Army and the Czechoslovaks, Summer, 1918"
      - Kolchak, Admiral--see South Russia/Leaders
      - Military Representative of the Supreme Ruler to the governments and headquarters of the Allies--see Administration of the Commander-in- Chief's Chief Representative of the Russian Army to the Government of French Republic
      - South Russia (Box 253)
        - Leaders (Folder 1)
        - Military administration (Folder 2)
        - Politics, Practical (Folder 3-4)
          Available on microfilm reel 309
      - War news--see Administration of the Commander-in- Chief's Chief Representative of the Russian Army to the Government of French Republic
    - Economic conditions--see Counterrevolutionary movements/Administration of Commander-in-Chief's Chief Representative of the Russian Army to the Government of French Republic
    - Foreign relations. Clippings
      - Great Britain, 1920
        - January-April (Folder 5)
        - April-July (Folder 6)
      - Japan (Folder 7)
      - United States (Folder 8)
    - Red Army--see Military Agent Office File/Akintievskii, G., Lieutenant-Colonel, "National Army and the Czechoslovaks, Summer, 1918"
  - Russian Embassy
    - Artillery Commission (Folder 9)
    - Commission on Promoting Fulfillment of the Orders Placed by Russian Imperial Government in the United States (Folder 10)
    - Commission for Reviewing Petitions for Assistance (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Consulate General, New York (Folder 2)
    - Division of Supplies
      - Financial Section (Folder 3)
      - General Chancery (Folder 4)
        Available on microfilm reel 310
      - General Section
        - 1919 (Folder 5)
        - 1920
          - Correspondence (Folder 6)
          - Orders (Folder 7)
    - Financial Agent
      - 1920 (Folder 8)
      - 1921 (Folder 9)
    - Naval Agent (Folder 10)
    - Russian Supply Committee
      - 1915-1916 (Folder 11)
      - 1918 (Folder 12)
      - 1920 (Folder 13)
  - Russian Information Bureau
    - 1919 (Folder 14)
    - 1919-1920 (Folder 15)
  - Russian intelligence service
    - Composition and structure
      - Instruction (Folder 16)
      - Reports (Folder 17)
    - Duras, Victor Hugo (Box 255, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 311
    - United States
      - 1915
        - General (Folder 2)
        - American rifle companies (Folder 3)
      - 1916 (Folder 4)
      - 1917
        - General
          - January-May (Folder 5)
          - April-May (Folder 6)
          - June-December (Folder 7)
        - Butskoi, Lieutenant (Folder 8)
        - Ribkovskii, Dmitrii (Folder 9)
      - 1918 (Folder 10)
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 11)
    - World politics (Box 256)
      - 1919-1920 (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 312
      - 1920 (Folder 2)
      - 1920-1921 (Folder 3)
  - Russian Red Cross -- censorship
    - Correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Register (Folder 5)
  - Russian Veterans in the United States
    - General
      - General
        - 1916-1921 (Folder 6-7)
          Available on microfilm reel 313
        - 1918 (Folder 8)
        - 1918-1919 (Box 257, Folder 1)
        - 1918-1920 (Folder 2)
      - Organizations
        - Stand by Russia Committee (Folder 3)
        - Union of Russian Navy and Army Officers in California (Folder 4)
        - Voluntary Association of Russian Navy and Army Officers in the United States
          - 1918
            - February-September (Folder 5)
            - September-November (Folder 6)
          - 1918-1919 (Folder 7)
            Available on microfilm reel 314
          - 1919 (Folder 8)
      - Representatives of Russian Military Agent in New York
        - 1918-1919 (Folder 9)
        - 1919 (Box 258)
          - February-November (Folder 1)
          - March-December (Folder 2)
        - 1919-1920 (Folder 3)
      - Return to Russia (Folder 4-6)
        Available on microfilm reel 315
    - Agafonov, Aleksandr, Non-Commissioned Officer (Folder 7)
    - Agapetian, Khan, General? (Folder 8)
    - Ageerv, Aleksandr, Ensign (Folder 9)
    - Aivaz-Ogly, Ensign (Folder 10)
    - Aksenov, Major-General (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Alekseev, Konstantin, Cornet (Folder 2)
    - Alekseev, Nikolai, Ensign (Folder 3)
    - Alenkevich, Andrei, Ensign (Folder 4)
    - Andrikis, Antonii, Second Captain (Folder 5)
    - Antipin, Petr, Ensign (Folder 6)
    - Anuf'er, Sergei, Second Captain (Folder 7)
    - Aronsberg, Emmanuil, Private (Folder 8)
    - Astapov, Ivan, Lieutenant (Folder 9)
    - Avksent'ev, V., Lieutenant (Folder 10)
    - Baldin, Siluan, Major-General (Folder 11)
    - Basov, Colonel (Folder 12)
    - Bek, Petr, Colonel (Folder 13)
    - Bekel', Aleksandr, Ensign (Folder 14)
    - Bel'dau, Konstantin, Cornet (Folder 15)
    - Beliaev, Mikhail, Non-Commissioned Officer (Folder 16)
    - Bem, Zenon, Lieutenant (Folder 17)
    - Ber, Lieutenant (Folder 18)
      Available on microfilm reel 316
    - Biskupskii, Major-General (Folder 19)
    - Bobovich, Viacheslav (Folder 20)
    - Bogdanov, Second Lieutenant (Folder 21)
    - Bogomolov, Konstantin, Ensign (Folder 22)
    - Bogoslovskii, Boris, Ensign (Folder 23)
    - Bogoslovskii, Boris, Lieutenant (Folder 24)
    - Braetskii, Second Captain (Folder 25)
    - Brazol', Boris, Ensign (Folder 26)
    - Burlin, General (Folder 27)
    - Burmistrov, Ivan (Folder 28)
    - Dabolin, Al'bert, Lieutenant (Folder 29)
    - Danilov, Sergei, Ensign (Folder 30)
    - Dedulov, A., Ensign (Folder 31)
    - Deriabin, Ensign (Folder 32)
    - Ditmar, Andrei, Lieutenant (Folder 33)
    - Ditmar, Georgii, Captain (Folder 34)
    - Ditsh, Vol'demar, Lieutenant (Folder 35)
    - Dmitriev, Boris, Lieutenant (Folder 36)
    - Dobrozhanskii, Aleksandr, Major-General (Folder 37)
    - Dolinskii, Captain (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Dombrovskii, Cornet (Folder 2)
    - Dronnikov, Nikolai, Lieutenant (Folder 3)
    - Dubasov, Dmitrii, Second Captain (Folder 4)
    - Duklau, Captain (Folder 5)
      Available on microfilm reel 317
    - Dunaevskii, Georgii, Colonel (Folder 6)
    - Dzheneev, Ivan, Ensign (Folder 7)
    - Egorov, Iakov, Captain (Folder 8)
    - Egorov, Mstislav (Folder 9)
    - Eremievskii, Sergei, Lieutenant (Folder 10)
    - Evreinov, Sergei, Captain (Folder 11)
    - Gadzevich, Mikhail, Colonel (Folder 12)
    - Garkun, P., Second Lieutenant (Folder 13)
    - Gassel'blatt, Colonel (Folder 14)
    - Gaveman, Viktor, Ensign (Folder 15)
    - Golovin, Nikolai, Lieutenant-Genenal (Folder 16)
    - Grozdov, Aleksandr, Ensign (Folder 17)
    - Grozdov, Igor', Ensign (Folder 18)
    - Gudima, Boris, Captain (Folder 19)
    - Gul'zhila, Fedor, Pilot (Folder 20)
    - Inostrantsev, Major-General (Folder 21)
    - Iogelevich, Mikhail, General (Folder 22)
    - Iogelevich, Pavel, Captain--see Iogelevich, Mikhail, General
    - Iogel'sen, Vladimir, Second Lieutenant (Folder 23)
    - Ipatov, Second Captain (Folder 24)
    - Ivanzhin, Second Captain (Folder 25)
    - Kal'nyn, Ivan (Folder 26)
    - Kalpashnikov-Kamak, Andrei, Colonel (Folder 27)
    - Kantakuzin, Major-General, Prince (Folder 28)
    - Karasev, Sergei, Second Lieutenant (Folder 29)
    - Karpov, Georgii, Lieutenant (Folder 30)
    - Kirillin, Luka, Second Captain (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Kirsanov, Major-General (Folder 2)
    - Kizeval'ter, Georgii (Folder 3)
    - Klembovskii, Georgii, Lieutenant-Colonel (Folder 4)
    - Koblianskii, Nikolai, Second Captain (Folder 5)
    - Kochubei, Viktor, Cornet, Prince (Folder 6)
    - Kokh, Nikolai, Colonel (Folder 7)
    - Kolesnikov, Lavrentii, Ensign (Folder 8)
    - Komissarov, General (Folder 9)
    - Kondzerovskii, Captain (Folder 10)
    - Konishenko, Colonel (Folder 11)
    - Korf, Semen, Lieutenant (Folder 12)
    - Korvin-Krukovskii, Boris, Second Lieutenant (Folder 13)
      Available on microfilm reel 318
    - Korzhibskii, Andrei, Private (Folder 14)
    - Kostenko, Mikhail, Second Lieutenant (Folder 15)
    - Kostomarov, Dmitrii, Major-General (Folder 16)
    - Kostritskii, Evgenii, Second Captain (Folder 17)
    - Kotliarevskii, N. (Folder 18)
    - Kovalev, Mikhail, Cornet (Folder 19)
    - Kozakovskii, Nikolai, Colonel (Folder 20)
    - Kravets, Ivan, Captain (Folder 21)
    - Krivitskii, Aleksandr, Colonel (Folder 22)
    - Krupskii, Georgii, Colonel (Folder 23)
    - Krupskii, Nikolai--see Krupskii, Georgii
    - Kulakov, Nikolai, Second Lieutenant (Folder 24)
    - Kul'chitskii, Georgii, Ensign (Folder 25)
    - Kustov, M. I., Second Captain (Folder 26)
    - Laguna, Genrikh, Second Lieutenant (Folder 27)
    - Lang, Boris, Second Captain (Folder 28)
    - Lange, Verner, Ensign (Folder 29)
    - Lazovert, Stanislav, Captain (Folder 30)
    - Liarskii, Georgii, Captain (Folder 31)
    - Limanskii, Boris, Lieutenant (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Lipskii, Nikolai, Second Lieutenant (Folder 2)
    - Lodyzhenskii, Fedor, Colonel (Folder 3)
    - Lugovoi, Boris, Second Captain (Folder 4)
    - Lukomskii, V. V., Captain (Folder 5)
    - Lutskii, Lieutenant (Folder 6)
    - Nekrasov, V. V., Colonel (Folder 7)
    - Tsorn, Mikhail, Captain (Folder 8)
    - Vadetskii, Viacheslav, Second Captain (Folder 9)
    - Varshavskii, Vladimir, Cornet (Folder 10)
    - Vege, Colonel (Folder 11)
    - Vel'ts, Frants-Avgustin, Lieutenant (Folder 12)
    - Voinov, Serapion, Military priest (Folder 13)
    - Vol'f, Sergei, Colonel, Baron (Folder 14)
    - Volkov, Nikolai (Folder 15)
    - Volosov, Markus, Private (Folder 16)
    - Vorob'ev, Aleksandr, Colonel (Folder 17)
    - Vysotskii, Evgenii, Captain (Folder 18)
    - Zadde, Artur, Captain (Folder 19)
    - Zaikovskii, Vladimir, Captain (Folder 20)
    - Zavalishin, Boris, Captain (Folder 21)
    - Zvaigsne, Warrant Officer? (Folder 22)
    - Zvorykin, Boris, Lieutenant (Folder 23)
  - United States
    - Armed forces--see Military Agent Office File/Odintsov, Colonel, ed., Vooruzhennye sily Severo-Amerikanskikh Soedinennykh Shtatov i drugikh gosudarstv Ameriki. St. Petersburg, 1910
      - General
        - General
          - 1917 (Folder 24)
          - 1917-1918 (Folder 25)
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 26)
            Available on microfilm reel 319
        - Clippings (Box 263, Folder 1)
        - Printed matter (Folder 2)
        - Reports
          - General (Folder 3)
          - Arms and armor (Folder 4)
          - Composition
            - General (Folder 5)
            - Officers (Folder 6)
          - Structure
            - General
              - Handwritten copy (Folder 7)
              - Typewritten copy (Folder 8)
              - Appendices (Folder 9)
            - General staff (Folder 10)
      - Air force
        - General (Folder 11)
          Available on microfilm reel 320
        - Reports (Box 264)
          - Korvin-Krukovskii, Boris, Second- Lieutenant (Folder 1)
          - Utgoft, Viktor, Lieutenant, 1919
            - August (Folder 2)
            - October? (Folder 3)
            - November (Folder 4)
      - Compulsory military service
        - General (Folder 5)
        - Employees of Russian agencies (Folder 6)
    - Labor and laboring classes. Clippings, 1920
      - March-October (Folder 7)
      - April-June (Folder 8)
    - Radio communication with other countries (Folder 9)
      Available on microfilm reel 321
    - Slavs (Folder 10)
  - Vrangel', Petr, General, Baron (Folder 11)
  - World politics--see Russian/Counterrevolutionary movements/ Administration of the Commander-in-Chief's Chief Representative of the Russian Army to the Government of French Republic; and Russian Intelligence service/World politics
- Naval Agent Office File, 1897-1920.
  Available on microfilm reels 321-365
  Administrative orders, blueprints, clippings, correspondence, financial records, memoranda, printed matter, reports, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General (Box 265)
    - Blueprints
      - 1904 (Folder 1)
      - 1915 (Folder 2)
    - Clippings
      - 1897-1902 (Folder 3)
      - 1917-1919
        - Volume 1 (Folder 4)
        - Volume 2 (Folder 5)
        - Volume 3? (Folder 6)
        - Volume 4 (Folder 7)
        - Volume 7 (Box 266, Folder 1)
        - Volume 9 (Folder 2)
        - Volume 10 (Folder 3)
        - Volume 11 (Folder 4)
        - Volume 12 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - General
          - n.d. (Folder 2)
          - 1897 (Folder 3)
          - 1898 (Folder 4)
          - 1899
            - January-April (Folder 5)
            - May-August (Folder 6)
            - September-December (Folder 7)
          - 1900 (Folder 8)
          - 1901
            - January-May (Folder 9)
              Available on microfilm reel 322
            - June-December (Folder 10)
          - 1902 (Box 268)
            - January-April (Folder 1)
            - May-December (Folder 2)
          - 1903
            - January-April (Folder 3)
            - January-December (Folder 4)
          - 1904
            - General
              - Letters and telegrams (Folder 5)
              - Telegrams (Folder 6)
                Available on microfilm reel 323
            - A (Folder 7)
            - B (Folder 8)
            - C (Folder 9)
            - D (Box 269, Folder 1)
            - E-F (Folder 2)
            - I-J (Folder 3)
            - K-L (Folder 4)
            - M (Folder 5)
            - N-O (Folder 6)
            - P-Q (Folder 7)
            - R (Folder 8)
            - S (Folder 9)
            - T-U (Folder 10)
            - W (Folder 11)
            - Y-Z (Folder 12)
          - 1905
            - General (Folder 13)
            - A (Folder 14)
              Available on microfilm reel 324
            - B (Folder 15)
            - C (Folder 16)
            - D (Folder 17)
            - F (Folder 18)
            - G (Folder 19)
            - H (Folder 20)
            - J (Folder 21)
            - K-L (Folder 22)
            - M (Folder 23)
            - P (Folder 24)
            - R (Folder 25)
            - S (Box 270, Folder 1)
            - T (Folder 2)
            - U (Folder 3)
            - W (Folder 4)
          - 1906
            - General (Folder 5)
            - A (Folder 6)
            - B (Folder 7)
            - C (Folder 8)
            - D (Folder 9)
            - E (Folder 10)
            - F (Folder 11)
            - G (Folder 12)
            - H-I (Folder 13)
              Available on microfilm reel 325
            - K-L (Folder 14)
            - M (Folder 15)
            - N-O (Box 271, Folder 1)
            - P-Q (Folder 2)
            - R (Folder 3)
            - S (Folder 4)
            - T (Folder 5)
            - U (Folder 6)
            - W (Folder 7)
          - 1907
            - General (Folder 8)
            - A (Folder 9)
            - B (Folder 10)
            - C (Folder 11)
            - D (Folder 12)
            - G (Folder 13)
            - H (Folder 14)
            - I-J (Folder 15)
            - K-L (Folder 16)
            - M (Folder 17)
            - N-O (Folder 18)
            - P-Q (Box 272, Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 326
            - R (Folder 2)
            - S (Folder 3)
            - T (Folder 4)
            - U-V (Folder 5)
            - W (Folder 6)
          - 1908
            - General (Folder 7)
            - A (Folder 8)
            - C (Folder 9)
            - D (Folder 10)
            - E (Folder 11)
            - F (Folder 12)
            - G (Folder 13)
            - H (Folder 14)
            - J (Folder 15)
            - K-L (Folder 16)
            - M (Folder 17)
            - N-O (Box 273, Folder 1)
              Available on microfilm reel 327
            - P-Q (Folder 2)
            - R (Folder 3)
            - S (Folder 4)
            - T (Folder 5)
            - U (Folder 6)
            - W (Folder 7)
          - 1909 (Folder 8)
          - 1911 (Folder 9)
          - 1912 (Folder 10)
          - 1914 (Folder 11)
        - Incoming
          - 1898-1899 (Folder 12)
          - 1900 (Box 274, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 328
          - 1901 (Folder 2)
          - 1905 (Box 275, Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 329
          - 1906-1908 (Folder 2)
          - 1909-1914 (Folder 3)
        - Outgoing
          - 1898-1900 (Folder 4)